Michael Tobias Flohrschütz

Audio engineer, AcroYoga and movement teacher, Bodyworker

After graduating high school, I started an audio engineering career. First working as audio technician for concerts and in recording studios. Then, after achieving the bachelor's degree in audio engineering, I specialized in room acoustics.

In 2012 I discovered AcroYoga and soon fell in love with it. I dedicated all my free time to traveling the world, studying AcroYoga, traditional and modern styles of Yoga, partner acrobatics, various other forms of movement (gymnastics, capoeira, contemporary dance, fitness, martial arts, Tai Chi), bodywork (Thai-massage, Cranial biodynamics, abdominal massage, FlyingBodywork), biomechanics and anatomy, as well as the spiritual wisdom of the east and west. In 2014 I started teaching AcroYoga at regular classes in Munich Germany, as well as at numerous retreats and festivals every year.



Work experience

2014 – present Self-employed AcroYoga teacher, organizing and teaching workshops,

(mainly in Munich Germany), as well as several retreats, festivals and

conventions every year

2013 – present Teacher for barefootyoga.me

1.1.2015 – 31.12.2015 Employment as Acoustics engineer for concept-A GmbH

2006 – 2013 Self-employed work as audio technician

Education

2007-2015 Bachelor of Science (BSc) in audio engineering ("Elektrotechnik –

Toningenieur") at technical university Graz and university of music and

performing arts Graz

2005-2007 Sound engineering diploma at Deutschen POP Akademie (Munich)

2004 High school graduation (Max-Planck-Gymnasium München)

Languages

Fluent spoken and written German and English. Basic Spanish and Italian.

Personal Info

Name: Michael Tobias Flohrschütz

Date of birth: 17.2.1984

Place of birth: Munich Germany

Email: FlyingMonkey@mail.de

Website: www.FlyingMonkey.eu

Phone: +49 163 163 1858